(ﾎｰｸ)ああ～ 効く～｡
Ah, that feels great!
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜聖騎士
ギルサンダーにより負わされた➡
The wounds inflicted upon Meliodas by the Holy Knight Gilthunder
メリオダスの傷は
思いのほか 深刻だった＞
were more serious than they seemed.
＜バステ監獄に捕らわれた
三人目の大罪➡
Continuing their efforts to rescue
the third Sin, the Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban,
who is currently imprisoned at Baste Dungeon,
強欲の罪 強欲の罪のバンを
救い出すべく訪れた➡
ダルマリーの町で 献身的に
看病に当たるエリザベス＞
Elizabeth tends to Meliodas's
wounds in the town of Dalmary.
＜ だが 嫉妬の罪
嫉妬の罪のディアンヌとは➡
However, the Serpent's Sin of Envy, Diane, continues to butt heads with Elizabeth.
すれ違いが続く＞
＜動きだす四人の聖騎士
｢不気味な牙｣＞
The four Holy Knights, the Weird Fangs, begin to make their moves.
Ban frees himself from his cell.
＜バンは 独房から外へ＞
＜ そして メリオダスには…＞
However,
as for Meliodas...
Who are you? Show yourself!
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)
誰なの!? 姿を現しなさい！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)お初に お目にかかります｡
はっ！
Allow me to introduce myself.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)我は ｢不気味な牙｣の一人
聖騎士ゴルギウス｡
I am the Holy Knight Golgius of the Weird Fangs.
Holy Knight...
聖騎士…｡
こいつ どっから？
Where'd he come from?
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)エリザベス王女 御身を➡
Princess Elizabeth, I have come to pick you up.
お迎えに上がりました｡
あっ｡
おっと！
Whoa there!
その前に 残飯処理騎士団
団長ホーク様が相手するぜ！
First you'll have to get past Hawk,
the captain of the Knights of Leftovers Disposal!
プギッ！ ボボボボッ…｡
ホークちゃん！
Hawk!
Besides...
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)それに…｡
There's no reason to leave this sword in your possession.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
この剣は 貴殿が所持していても➡
無意味なものです｡
お返しいただきましょう｡
I'll just be taking this back.
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜国を守る聖騎士たちは
絶大なる魔力を有し➡
The Holy Knights who protected this country
wielded immensely powerful magic.
恐れ 敬われた＞
They were both feared and revered.
＜ だが その中で 国を裏切り➡
However,
a faction arose who betrayed their country and turned their blades against the remaining Knights.
全聖騎士を
敵に回した者たちがいた＞
＜人々は
彼らを 七つの大罪と呼んだ＞
To the masses, they were known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 5
Even if You Were to Die
10 Years Ago
(ﾊﾞﾝ･回想)
((なあ 団ちょ いいだろ～？➡
Hey, Cap'n....
C'mon!
Lemme have a look at that sword.
その剣 見せてくれよ～))
What's so interesting about this piece of junk?
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)((こんな刃折れの剣を見て
何が楽しいんだよ))
Why would the captain of the Sins always
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((七つの大罪の
団長ともあろう者が➡
carry a piece of junk with him wherever he goes?
な～んで
そんな剣 持ち歩いてんのか➡
気にならない方が
おかしいってぇ～の))
It'd be weird if I wasn't at least a little curious.
((なあ 見せてくれって))
C'mon, show me.
Oh?
((あっ))
((放せ バン))
Let go, Ban.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)((んん…
二人とも まだ起きてるの？))
What're you two still doing up?
Let go, Ban.
((放せ バン｡ 俺を怒らせるな))
Don't make me angry.
Cap'n... Angry?
((怒る？ 団ちょが？))
((あんたと
つるんで もう何年にもなるけど➡
I've been with you for many years, but...
一度でも
怒ったとこ見たことないぜ？))
I haven't even seen you get angry once.
Let go.
((放せ))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((つぅか➡
Besides, I'm curious as to why you're
called the Sin of Wrath in the first place.
そもそも 団ちょが
憤怒の罪って呼ばれる理由にも➡
興味あるんだよな～))
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
((バン 団長に 何してるの？))
Ban, what are you doing to Captain?!
All this talk of Cap'n actually getting angry
((団ちょの怒るとこが
見られるっていうなら➡
ますます 剣が見たく…
いや 奪いたくなった))
makes me really want to see the sword—no, to steal it!
((へえ～
団ちょの隠れた一面 新発見))
So that's Cap'n's hidden side.
A new discovery.
((悪いな バン｡ この剣は…))
I'm sorry, Ban, but this sword is...
Stop it! What are you doing to Lord Meliodas?!
やめて！
メリオダス様に何をするの!?
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
ふん！ なるほど この剣ですか｡➡
I see... So it's this sword.
ん!?
(ﾀﾞﾅ)バ… バカな！
I-Impossible!
猛毒を あれほど飲ませたのに｡
Even after all that poison...
You just refuse to die.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)死に損ないが…｡➡
剣から 手を放しなさい！
Let go of the sword!
この剣は
死んでも離すわけにはいかねぇ｡
I can never let go of this sword, even if I die.
That is the one and only thing I can do to atone for my sins!
それが
俺にできる 唯一の償いなんだ｡
メリオダス様？
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)イヒヒヒ！➡
Lord Meliodas!
どんな戯言を言おうと
王女と この剣は頂きますよ｡
Your heroic words mean nothing!
I'm taking the sword and the princess!
パリーン！
逃げやがった｡
He got away!
Um... You're still Lord Meliodas,
あの…
メリオダス様… ですよね？
aren't you?
Yo, Elizabeth and the ass-hog.
よう｡ エリザベスに豚野郎｡
Thank goodness!
よかった
いつものメリオダス様だ｡
That sounds like the Lord Meliodas I know.
But this guy just called me ass-hog.
でも こいつ
豚野郎って言ったぜ｡
Hey, where are we?
なあ ここどこ？
ダルマリーの町です｡
バステ監獄手前の｡
The town of Dalmary.
It's close to Baste Dungeon.
さっきの変なヤツは？
And who was that guy just now?
A Holy Knight called Golgius or something.
ゴルギウスとかいう聖騎士だ｡
どうも エリザベスちゃんと
お前の刃折れの剣を➡
Seemed like he was after
Elizabeth and your broken sword.
狙ってるみてぇだったぜ｡
That rotten doctor's with him too.
そこのクソ医者が
グルになって…｡
Huh?
あら？
バックレやがったか！ 追うぜ！
He ran away! Let's go after him!
Wait!
待って！ メリオダス様の傷は
まだ癒えていないのよ｡
Meliodas still hasn't fully recovered!
エリザベスちゃん 痛いっす…｡
ん？
Elizabeth, that really hurt!
なんか治ってる｡
Looks like it's healed.
Wh-What? No way!
そっ そんな…｡ うそ!?
どうしたんだ？
What's wrong?
You're awfully assertive today.
今日は やけに積極的だな｡
えっ？
いや あっ… そういう意味じゃ…｡
No, it's not like that!
どんどん触っていいぞ｡
ほれ ほ～れ｡
Feel free to touch me some more. Come on!
But that's...
でも そんな…｡
いいから 早く服着ろや｡
Hurry up and put some clothes on.
God, that was close.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)いやはや危機一髪｡➡
あれが憤怒の罪のメリオダスか｡➡
So that's the Dragon's Sin of Wrath, Meliodas.
If I had retreated even a moment later...
あと一瞬 あそこから
撤退するのが遅れていたら…｡➡
イヒヒヒ… うん 面白い｡
Yeah.
Interesting.
There!
いた｡
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)おっと｡➡
Whoops.
見つかっちゃいましたか？
１マイル先の➡
Looks like I've been caught.
Don't underestimate my nose that
can smell leftovers from a mile away!
残飯の匂いを嗅ぎ分ける
俺様の鼻をなめんなよ！
それ 本当？
うん！
Is that true?
Yep! Interested?
えっ ひいた？
この剣と王女を➡
You're going to tell us who sent you after the princess and my sword.
奪うように命令したのは誰か
教えてもらうぞ｡
でなきゃ
お前を 今すぐボコボコに…｡
If not, things will get troublesome—
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)はい！ 降参でございます｡
えっ？
Okay! I surrender!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)このゴルギウス
生来 臆病なたちでして➡
I, Golgius, am of a cowardly nature and dislike fighting to begin with.
戦いは好みません｡ ましてや➡
Especially against someone like
the captain of the legendary Seven.
相手が 七つの大罪の団長であれば
なおのこと｡
ガキン！ ガキン！
(２人)えっ？
I threw those assassination blades the moment I raised my hands.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)手を上げた瞬間に放った
暗器ですが➡
やっぱり見破られちゃいました？
Did you actually notice them?
Don't underestimate my eyes that can see exposed panties from a mile away.
１マイル先の
パンチラを見逃さない➡
俺の眼力をなめんな｡
ほ… 本当ですか？
I-Is that true?
うそ｡
ゴルギウス様！
Nope.
Lord Golgius, there you are!
そこにおられましたか｡
あっ あのクソ医者！
I-It's the rotten doctor!
Although I didn't manage to kill him,
少年を殺すことには
失敗しましたが➡
I made him drink the poison as instructed!
言われたとおり
毒は飲ませました｡
Please return my daughter like you promised!
約束どおり 娘を返してください！
He's gone?!
消えた｡
ど… どこ行った？
Wh-Where'd he go?
Elizabeth, stay close.
エリザベス 離れんなよ｡
はい｡
Yes!
Come to think of it, he's always appearing out of nowhere!
そういや さっきも 何もない所から
急に現れやがったんだ｡
No need to raise your voice.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)声を荒げるな｡
娘は お前のもとへ返してやろう｡
I will return your daughter to you.
あ… ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
あっ おい！ そこから逃げろ！
Hey, get away from there!
In the next world, where she'll be joining you shortly.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
あの世へ逝く お前のもとへね｡
ドスッ！
ぐおっ！
あっ！
やりやがった｡
He's really done it!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)聖騎士が
子供１人に毒殺を命じたなどと➡
There'd be serious trouble if word got out that the Holy Knights are ordering people to poison kids.
無駄な悪評を立てられるのは
困るんだよね｡
ダナ先生！
エリザベス！
Dr. Dana!
Elizabeth!
Just leave that bastard alone!
んなヤツは ほっとけって！
ダナ先生 しっかり！
Dr. Dana, hang on!
ここは危険だ｡ あいつが また
いつどこから現れるか分からねぇ｡
It's dangerous here!
We have no idea where he'll appear next!
But we can't just leave Dr. Dana to die!
でも ダナ先生を見殺しには…｡
あっ！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)そ～～れっ！
Take this!
っと… と！ んんっ！
Lord Meliodas!
メリオダス様！
また消えた！
He disappeared again?
これって瞬間移動ってやつじゃね!?
Is this what they call teleportation?
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)イヒヒヒ！
利口な豚さんですねぇ｡➡
You're a smart pig.
そう 私の瞬間移動の前には➡
Yes, all your powers are useless against my teleportation!
どんな力も役に立ちません｡
えっ!? うわっ！
きゃあ！
We've gotta run for it!
ひとまず走るぞ！
あっ｡
トンドコドコドコ
トンドコドコドコ トンドコ…｡
あっ… きゃあ！ うっ！
くっそ～！ こいつの
鉄臭ぇ臭いの筋は感じるんだが｡
Dammit!
I can trace his metallic smell, but...
くんくん…｡
こう忙しいと たどってる暇がねぇ｡
If we're running, there's nothing we can do!
Trace his smell...
臭いの筋？
ガキン！
ぐっ！
ドカッ！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)イヒヒ！
どこに逃げ隠れしようと➡
No matter where you run or hide, I will find and corner you.
必ず 追い詰めますよ｡
トンドコドンドン…｡
はぁ はぁ はぁ…｡
こっちだ！
トンドコドンドン…｡
Here!
なんで こんな荒家に
逃げ込んじまうんだよ？
Why are we hiding in this abandoned building?
ホーク お前
町の人間 巻き込むつもりか？
Hawk, were you planning on getting the townsfolk involved in this?
Well, that's true, but...
そ… そりゃまあ そうだけど｡
Let's wait here until he's gone.
ここで
しばらく ヤツをやり過ごすか｡
But man, what a rundown building.
しっかし ボロもいいとこだぜ｡
ああ～ カビ臭ぇ｡
It's so moldy in here.
What are you doing?
何してんだ？
ん？
A magic spell that'll keep him outta here.
あいつを
ここに入れない まじない｡
Magic my ass.
何が まじないだよ｡
んなもん できもしねぇくせに｡
There's no way that'll do anything.
果たして そうかな？
We'll see about that.
Are you sure about this?
でも いいのか？
こんな狭い荒家の➡
We're on the top floor of
a narrow abandoned building.
最上階って…｡
逃げ場はねぇぜ？
There's nowhere to escape.
Close the door, at the very least.
せめて 扉くらい閉めとけよ｡
If he can teleport, the door won't do anything.
瞬間移動に 扉は関係ねぇだろ｡
いきなり 俺たちの真ん中に
出てくるかもしんねぇんだぜ｡
He could just appear in the middle of the room.
うっ… 怖っ！
S-Scary!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
残念 後ろですよ｡ イヒヒ…｡
Too bad.
I'm behind you.
残念 足元ですよ｡ にししっ！
Too bad, it's underneath you.
バキン！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)ああっ!? ぐわっ！➡
あっ！ どわぁ…｡
あぁ～あ➡
荒家だけに 真下まで行ったな｡
He fell all the way to the bottom of this building.
さっきの まじないって…｡
So your spell earlier was to...
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
ぐっ… 入り口の床に切り込みが｡
A cut on the floor of the entrance?
透明化だろ？ お前の魔力｡
So your power's invisibility, huh?
I couldn't figure out why it took you some time to reappear after you vanished.
お前が 姿を消してから
次の場所に現れるまでの間が➡
な～んか気になってたんだよなぁ｡
It was weird that we could trace your smell even though you "teleported."
瞬間移動で
臭いの筋が出来るのも変だし｡
In other words, you've been
moving at the same speed as us.
つまり お前は 俺たちと同じく
歩いて移動してたわけだ｡
Which means that the door was the only way you could get in.
ってことは
当然 １つしかない扉から➡
部屋に入ってくる｡
ついでに ここなら➡
Also, since we're down here,
I don't need to worry about Elizabeth.
俺も
エリザベスに気を遣う必要がない｡
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)ひぃ！
キン！
ドーン！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)ぐわぁ～～！➡
ぐはっ…｡
Well now, let's hear it, Li'l Golgius.
さてさてさ～て
答えてもらおうかな➡
ゴルギウスちゃん｡
お前が 俺の剣と
エリザベスを狙う理由と➡
Why are you after Elizabeth and
my sword? Who put you up to it?
それを 誰が命令したのか｡
メリオダス様！
Lord Meliodas!
For a second there I thought you were a goner!
一時は どうなることかと思ったぜ｡
あっ！
ありゃま 逃げちゃった｡
Oh my, he got away.
≫ヒヒーン！(馬の鳴き声)
ひぃ！
な… なんだ 馬かよ｡
Oh, it's just a horse.
It probably got frightened by the loud noise earlier.
さっきの轟音に ビビったんだな｡
臆病な動物だぜ｡
Such a timid animal.
There, huh?
あそこだな｡
えっ？ うわっ！
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
ひぃ… ああ～ 怖い 怖い｡➡
So scary.
The brass gave me such a crazy mission.
上も とんだ任務を
与えてくれたものです｡
馬が向かう先は バステ監獄だな｡
よっしゃ 行こうぜ！
The horse must be headed toward Baste Dungeon.
All right, let's go then!
あっ おい エリザベス？
Hey, Elizabeth!
そっちは バステ監獄じゃねぇぞ！
Baste Dungeon's not that way!
Doctor! Doctor Dana!
先生！ ダナ先生！
Pull yourself together!
しっかりしてください｡
どうして こんな…｡
Why did this...
なぜ… 君が泣くのだね？➡
Why... are you crying for me?
I'm sorry...
すまな… かった｡➡
娘を… 助けたいばかりに 私は…｡
I just wanted... to save my daughter...
Cenette...
セネット… お前を➡
I just wanted... to protect...
守ってあげたかった…｡
you...
うぅ… 私のせいで…｡
何言ってんだよ｡
It's all my fault...
What're you talking about?
Golgius killed the doctor.
先生を殺したのは
ゴルギウスだろ｡
私たちが この町に来なければ
ダナ先生は 死ぬことも➡
If we didn't come to this town...
Dr. Dana wouldn't have died,
聖騎士に お嬢さんを
人質に取られることも➡
and his daughter wouldn't have been
taken hostage by the Holy Knights, right?
なかったんですよね？
エリザベスちゃん…｡
Elizabeth...
And if I hadn't found Lord Meliodas while searching for the Seven Deadly Sins,
そもそも
私が 七つの大罪を捜して➡
メリオダス様と会わなければ➡
メリオダス様が
ギルサンダーとの戦いで➡
you wouldn't have suffered a serious injury fighting with Lord Gilthunder,
大ケガを負うことも
ゴルギウスの策略で➡
or nearly killed by Golgius's scheme!
殺されそうになることも
なかったんです｡
泣きたい気持ちぐらいは分かるさ｡
I understand why you're crying.
But...
でも お前が 王国と人々を➡
Is your desire to protect the
kingdom from the Holy Knights
聖騎士から守りてぇって思いは➡
涙１つや２つで
折れちまう程度のもんなのか？
so easily broken by just a few tears?
俺は
エリザベスと 七つの大罪を捜し➡
I resolved to find the other Sins
with you and stop the Holy Knights.
聖騎士を食い止めると決めた｡
Even if you were to die,
たとえ お前が死んでも
俺は お前との約束を果たす｡
I would fulfill the promise I made with you.
メリオダス… 様…｡
Lord Meliodas...
人は いつか死ぬ｡
Everyone has to die someday.
But...
でも その思いを
誰かが守り続けるかぎり➡
What they believed in will never fade away as long as someone protects it.
思いは死なねぇ｡
Once you've made the decision
思いを守ると決めたら➡
どれだけ血を流そうと
涙の１滴まで からそうと➡
to protect those principles no
matter the cost in blood and tears...
貫き通す｡
You follow through with it!
それが騎士だ｡
That's what it means to be a knight.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)いや～ 参った 参った｡➡
Man, what a beating.
あそこまでやるとは
思わなかったなぁ｡➡
I didn't expect him to be so powerful.
って… こっちも お出迎えの準備は
出来てるみたいね｡
But it looks like the welcoming party's all ready.
そんじゃ
ぼちぼち バステに向かうか｡
Well, let's get going to Baste Dungeon then, shall we?
なあ エリザベスちゃんを
置いていく気か？
Hey, you're not gonna leave Elizabeth behind, right?
あのダメ医者を診療所に
運んだきり 出てこねぇぜ｡
She hasn't come out of the clinic ever
since she carried that useless doctor in.
バ～カ いいんだよ
この町で じっとしてた方が｡
Stupid. She'll be much better off laying low in town.
バステにゃ
ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽを狙う聖騎士もいるんだぞ｡
There are Holy Knights at Baste who are after her as well.
ったく バカだな お前｡
バカって ２回言ったな！
Geez, how stupid can you be?
You called me stupid twice, didn't you?
バカって言うヤツが
バカ野郎なんだぞ！
Well, it takes one to know one!
悪かった 豚野郎｡
豚野郎だって同じだ この野郎！
My bad, ass-hog.
Calling me an ass-hog is no different at all, you bastard!
痛ててっ！ 皮が伸びる～…｡
You're stretching my skin...
メリオダス様～！
はぁ はぁ はぁ…｡
Lord Meliodas!
なんだよ？ 息 切らして｡
これ｡
Why are you out of breath?
Here.
I fixed it for you while you were sleeping.
メリオダス様が眠ってる間に
直しときました｡
It's not that great, but...
あんまり上手じゃないですけど｡
ええ子やん｡
Such a good girl!
サンキュー エリザベス｡
よかった｡
Thanks, Elizabeth!
Happy to help!
All right, let's go!
では さあ 出発！
私は騎士じゃありません｡ けど➡
I may not be a knight,
but...
私も 王国と人々を守るために
戦い続けます｡
I will keep fighting for the kingdom and its people.
Even if you were to die right now, Lord Meliodas.
たとえ メリオダス様が
今 死んでしまったとしても｡
今すぐ殺すなよ｡
す… すみません！
Don't be killing me now.
S-Sorry!
エリザベスちゃん！
俺が死んだら？ 俺が死んだら？
Elizabeth! What about me? What if I died?
あっ え～っと… 頑張るね｡
Oh, um... I'd do my best?
Elizabeth, the difference in your attitude is so cruel!
エリザベスちゃん
その対応の差は あんまりだぜ｡
ご… ごめんなさい ホークちゃん｡
安心しろ ホーク｡
I-I'm sorry, Hawk!
Don't worry, Hawk.
If you were to die...
お前が死んでも
その肉は無駄にしねぇ｡
I wouldn't let your meat go to waste!
なっ？ エリザベス｡
はい！
Right, Elizabeth?
Yes!
俺の思いは どうなるよ!?
What about how I feel?!
Let's go!
じゃ 行くか｡
は… はい！ バン様を助けに｡
Y-Yes!
Let's go save Lord Ban!
違うだろ？
えっ？
Not just yet.
Eh?
Cenette, was it?
まずは セネットだっけ？
ダナ先生の娘を助け出さねぇとな｡
We've gotta save Dr. Dana's daughter.
メリオダス様！
Lord Meliodas!
Oh, but what about Lord Ban?
あっ でも バン様は？
俺たちが
向かっていることさえ分かりゃ➡
Well, if he knows that we're on the way, he'll probably just bust himself out.
一人で 勝手に出てくるから｡
そうなんですか？
Really?
ドスン！
て… 敵襲か!? えっ？
Enemy attack?!
Diane!
ディアンヌ！
こんな所で 何してんだ？
What are you doing here?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長？ 団長！➡
Captain?
Captain! You're supposed to be resting!
まだ寝てなきゃダメだよ！
もう～ 何やってんの!?
What are you doing up and about?
Enough about me. Are you okay?
俺のことよか お前こそ大丈夫か？
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)大丈夫って… 僕が？
You're asking if I'm okay?
てめぇ ダルマリーで
虫をぶっ潰したあと➡
After you crushed all the bugs in Dalmary,
バステ監獄に
突進していったんじゃねぇのか？
you went charging toward Baste Dungeon, didn't you?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)はあ？ そうだっけ？
Huh? Did I?
ディアンヌ様？
Lady Diane?
Sounds like there's a really troublesome enemy.
こりゃ
厄介な相手がいるみてぇだなぁ｡
Are you really okay, Diane?
ほんとに大丈夫か？ ディアンヌ｡
Uh, yeah.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)う… うん｡
ちょっと ぼんやりしてるだけ…｡
I'm just a little out of it.
チリーン(鈴の音)
あっ｡
(ﾙｲﾝ)わしは 聖騎士ルイン｡
｢不気味な牙｣にして➡
I am Ruin, Holy Knight of the Weird Fangs,
here to bring ruin upon the Seven Deadly Sins.
七つの大罪に滅びを与える者｡
A Holy Knight!
聖騎士！
団長！ 王女さんを守って…➡
Captain, protect the prin—
あっ 団長？ みんな？
どこに行ったの!?
Captain? Guys? Where did everybody go?
(ﾙｲﾝ)ファファファ…
もはや ヤツらは わしの手中じゃ｡
They're already in my hands.
Give Captain back!
団長を返せ！
ドスン！
メリオダス様！
ひょええ～！
Lord Meliodas!
メリオダス様～！
よっ！ ふぅ～｡
Lord Meliodas!
ディアンヌ
いきなり お前 なんのまねだ？
Diane! What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Lady Diane! Lord Meliodas is right here!
ディアンヌ様
メリオダス様は ここです！
何 寝ぼけてんだよ デカ女！
What, are you sleepwalking or something, big girl?
Let me just say this now:
I won't lose to some Holy Knight!
言っとくけど
聖騎士なんかに 僕は負けない！
う～ん あの目…➡
Those eyes...
She can't see us at all.
完全に 俺たちが見えてねぇな｡
どっ どど… どうするよ？
きゃあ！
Wh-Wh-What should we do?!
逃げるか ひとまず｡
やっぱり そうなんのかよ！
We're running, duh!
I knew it!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)はあっ！ ふん！ はあ～！
トンドコドコドコ トンドコ…｡
ん？
やっべぇぞ 通行人だ！
お～い！
Uh-oh, innocent bystanders!
Hey!
You two had better run!
死にたくなけりゃ
あんたらも逃げろ！
(子供)えっ？
トンドコドコドコ…｡
うわっ… うわぁ～！
ドスン！
どこに隠れた!? 聖騎士！
あんたみたいなチビは➡
Where are you hiding, Holy Knight?
A midget like you should be smashed, twisted, and torn apart in your armor!
鎧ごとねじって ちぎって
すり潰してやる！
お助け～！
メリオダス様➡
Someone help!
Lord Meliodas, what's happened to Lady Diane?
ディアンヌ様は 一体
どうしてしまったんでしょうか？
んん～
どうかしちゃったのは確かだなぁ｡
There's definitely something going on with her.
ちょっと このチビ頼むわ｡
はっ はい｡
Keep an eye on this little guy.
O-Okay!
っと！
あなたたちは こんな所で何を？
What were you guys doing out here?
ううっ… 僕たち 羊飼いで➡
We're shepherds from Dalmary.
牧場からの帰りなんだ｡
We were just returning from the pasture.
ねえ 僕たち どうなっちゃうの？
What's gonna happen to us?
心配しなくても大丈夫｡
There's no need to worry.
He'll protect us.
あの人が きっと…｡
チリーン
あっ｡
お前は…｡
(ﾙｲﾝ)わしは 聖騎士ルイン｡➡
You're—?
I am Ruin, Holy Knight of the Weird Fangs,
｢不気味な牙｣にして
七つの大罪に滅びを与える者｡
here to bring ruin upon the Seven Deadly Sins.
Hey, you big oaf!
おい でかブツ！ お前か？
You're the one who did something weird to Diane, aren't you?
ディアンヌに
妙な技をかけたのは｡
You're... speaking to Diane...
っていうか
ディアンヌじゃん｡
(ﾙｲﾝ)ふん！
ドゴン！
ディアンヌを 元に戻せ！
Return Diane to the way she was before!
まっ まさか メリオダスまで
ディアンヌと同じように➡
No, it can't be!
Even Meliodas is under the effects of a spell just like Diane?
幻 見ちまってるんじゃね!?
んんっ！
ドカッ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)はあっ！
ドゴン！
キン！
んんっ！
ふん！
うわぁ～！
来た 来た 来た 来た～！
Run, run, run!
キン！
はあっ！
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ドゥフフフ！
ルインのおっさんってば➡
Old man Ruin is really getting into this!
張り切っちゃって まあ｡➡
ドゥフフフ！ それじゃあ
私も お仕事しないとね～｡
Guess I should join in on the fun soon, too.
What should we do, Elizabeth?
どうする？ エリザベスちゃん｡
ど… どうしましょう？
このままじゃ みんな…｡
What should we do?
If this keeps going...
What am I supposed to do?
一体 どうしたらいいの？
(騎士)ジェリコ様！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)七つの大罪➡
Lady Jericho!
Find him! Find the Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban!
強欲の罪のバンを捜せ！
B-But, Lady Jericho...
し… しかし ジェリコ様…｡
(騎士)そ… そのお姿は？
Y-You're...
It's fine! Just bring me a change of clothes and armor!
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)いいから！
俺の 替えの服と鎧を持ってこい！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)早く行け～！
(一同)は… はい～！
Hurry up and go!
Yes, ma'am!
(騎士)おおっ！
ぐっ… おのれ～！
That bastard!
((殺せ… すぐに殺せ！))
Kill me! Kill me now!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((散髪屋))
Listen, hairdresser...
((ごほっ ごほっ))
That's a nice set of armor you've got there.
((うっ))
((お前には似合わねぇ))
Doesn't really suit you, though.
バン… この恨み
必ずや晴らしてみせるぞ！
Ban...
I will get you back for this!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ああ～ やっぱ小さすぎか｡➡
Ah, guess it's too small.
せっかく気に入ったのに｡
≫(衛兵)出口付近を捜せ！
That's a real shame.
I liked the look of it.
Cut off all the exits!
≫(騎士)
通風孔に隠れてるかもしれんぞ！
He might be hiding in the vents!
さっきから うるせぇな～｡
誰か脱獄でもしたのか？
It's been noisy for a while...
Did someone escape or something?
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)どこへ行くつもりだ？➡
Where exactly do you think you're going?
Ban of the Seven Deadly Sins.
七つの大罪 バン｡
Hey, if it isn't the Holy Knight Jude.
よ～う 聖騎士ジュド｡
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)貴様は
ここで死ぬのだ バン｡ 私が殺す｡
You are going to die here, Ban.
And I shall be the one to kill you.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)俺を殺す？ 今更 なぜだ？
You're gonna kill me?
Why now, of all times?
You are of no more use to us.
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)用済みということだな｡
貴様は 七つの大罪団長を➡
You were the bait for the captain of the Sins,
and you've fulfilled that role.
おびき寄せる餌の役目を
十分に果たしてくれた｡➡
Right now, the other Weird Fangs are disposing of two members of the Seven Deadly Sins.
今頃 我ら｢不気味な牙｣の手で
七つの大罪の二人➡
The Dragon's Sin of Wrath, Meliodas, and the Serpent's Sin of Envy, Diane.
憤怒の罪のメリオダスと
嫉妬の罪のディアンヌは➡
始末されているだろう｡➡
And once I kill you, there will be
four fewer criminals in this world.
そして 貴様を殺せば
すでに死亡している者も含め➡
四人の大罪人が
この世から消えるのだ｡
くくくっ
その夢がかなうといいなぁ｡
I sure hope all your dreams come true.
Five years ago, who was it that caught and tortured you?
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)５年前 貴様を捕らえ
拷問にかけたのが誰か➡
忘れたわけではあるまい？
You haven't forgotten, have you?
じゃ 行くわ｡
Well, I'll be going.
ドスッ！
ああっ…｡
ぐはっ！
Next Episode's Report
The Seven's Deadly Sins' Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban, has escaped from prison!
＜七つの大罪 強欲の罪
強欲の罪のバンが脱獄した！＞
Cap'n?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)団ちょ～｡➡
Cap'n, where are you?
団ちょ どこだよ～？➡
Come on, Cap'n! Answer me!
ねえ 団ちょってばぁ｡➡
返事してくれよ～｡
The reunion between Ban and Meliodas's crew is still to come.
＜メリオダスたちと
バンとの再会は➡
まだまだ先のようである＞
Next time on The Seven Deadly Sins: "The Verse of the Beginning."
次回 『七つの大罪』
｢はじまりの詩｣｡
Cap'n!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)団ちょ～！ お～い！
Come on!
Episode 6
The Beginning of the Poem
Come on!
原子力発電所での重大事故を想定
した
国の原子力総合防災訓練が始まり､